# DYLAN DUSENBERRY

MARKETING COORDINATOR
CUSTOMER SERVICE

Working hard to understand the needs of customers and delivering effective marketing solutions that increase company growth.

### PERSONALITY HIGHLIGHTS

- Cheerful disposition
- Neat and well-organized
- Motivated by problem solving
- Independent worker & Team player
- Works well with deadlines
- Collaborative and efficient

## CONTACT DETAILS

855 Hinman Avenue, Apt 110 Evanston, IL 60202

dylan.dusenberry@yahoo.com

Mobile: 630.525.1132

REFERENCES AVAILABLE UPON REQUEST

# BASIC INFORMATION

I am a professional marketing coordinator with personable style who enjoys working with customers to ensure complete satisfaction. I am a hard working team player who is dependable and responsible, passionate about everything I do and am dedicated to providing exceptional work. My professional experience stems from years of providing excellent customer support, creative problem solving and activating marketing.

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

MARKETING COORDINATOR | HFI June 2015 - November 2017

Assisting and coordinating marketing projects for clients as requested. Organizing the production of branded items such as stationery and merchandise. Producing additional marketing communications: marketing decks, flyers, brochures and exhibition-related projects. Setting up tracking systems for marketing campaigns and online activities in Insightly and Mailchimp. Scheduling meetings and coordinating plans for accounts.

ASSISTANT MANAGER | SPERRY June 2014 - June 2015

Worked in conjunction with Oakbrook GM to lead a team of 15. Managed customer service comments and concerns while providing staff assistance and guidance daily. Created tasks and challenges to push individual sales goals and overall sales for 4 wall. Aware of surrounding environment and ensured conditions were safe for both our staff/customers

SUPERVISOR/TRAINER/MARKETING INTERN | MEATHEADS May 2013 - June 2014

Led a floor staff team of 10. Opened / closed location, managed weekly scheduling and breaks, Worked with HQ to brainstorm marketing ideas, work local events and fundraisers. Met with current and prospective clients to provide marketing collateral. Became HQ company trainer: travelled to all restaurant locations, corrected employee behavior/working habits, and trained all new hires, Emailed reviews and day to day communications to the district manager.

### **EDUCATION**

Glenbard West High School, Graduating Class of 2010 Columbia College Chicago- Bachelors in Interior Architecture (did not complete)